Guide to the Henry R. Luce Papers 1894-2004 (bulk, 1932-1967) MS 3014
New-York Historical Society
- Series V. Subject Name Files, 1894-1995 (bulk 1933-1967); 205880; 30.1 Linear feet
  - Subseries V.A. Name Files A, 1894-1995 (bulk 1933-1967); 205881
    - Me-Mi - General (folder 1 of 2), 1937-1967; 216793 (Box 96, Folder 3)
      Includes a copy of the article "Military Business and the Arms Race" by Stanislav Menshikov with related correspondence, and issues of the publication Propaganda Analysis: A Monthly Letter to Help the Intelligent Citizen Detect and Analyze Propaganda from Clyde R. Miller, Secretary of the Institute for Propaganda Analysis. Correspondents include George V. Melas, G.S. Meloy Jr., H.L. Mencken (telegram), and Lauritz Melchior.
    - Mi - General (folder 2 of 2), 1942-1965; 216794 (Box 96, Folder 4)
      Includes issues of the newsletter The Messenger from Richmond P. Miller. Correspondents include J. Irwin Miller and Wilbur D. Mills.
    - Meek, Samuel, 1936-1950; 216803 (Box 96, Folder 5)
    - Mehta, Gaganvihari Lallubhai, 1953; 216804 (Box 96, Folder 5)
      Includes a letter from Eric Johnston, President of the Motion Picture Association of America, Inc.
    - Merz, Charles, 1940-1949; 216805 (Box 96, Folder 5)
    - Meyer, Eugene (Mr. and Mrs.), 1937-1955; 216806 (Box 96, Folder 5)
      Includes the pamphlet "British Home Front" by Agnes E. Meyer.
    - Millis, Walter, 1940-1954; 216807 (Box 96, Folder 5)
    - Mo-My - General, 1933-1967; 216810 (Box 96, Folder 6)
      Includes a photograph of Charles S. Mott and HRL speaking at a China Relief event. Correspondents include Charles Mohr, Ward Morehouse, deLesseps S .Morrison, Elizabeth C. Morrow, Lewis Mumford, Frank Murphy, and Edward R. Murrow.
    - Mondadori, Arnaldo, 1953-1971; 216811 (Box 97, Folder 1)
    - Moore, Garrett, 1952; 216812 (Box 97, Folder 1)
      Includes an issue of the magazine History Today.
    - Moran, Breck, 1940; 216813 (Box 97, Folder 2)
      Includes the 7 February 1940 issue of the newspaper The Cody Enterprise.
    - Morano, Albert P., 1947-1959; 216814 (Box 97, Folder 2)
      Includes a letter from Carroll D. Kearns, text of the address made by Morano at the Bridgeport Chamber of Commerce luncheon, and copies of correspondence dealing with requests to appoint Clare Boothe Luce as Secretary of State.
    - Morgenthau, Jr. Henry, 1938-1963; 216815 (Box 97, Folder 2)
      Includes a draft from the Letters section of TIME titled "Morgenthau's Forecast" which was not published.
    - Morlion, Father Felix, 1954-1965; 216816 (Box 97, Folder 2)
      Includes a memorandum on the study project "The Philosophy and Practice of Private Enterprise in America and Italy."
    - Moses, Robert, 1933-1965; 216817 (Box 97, Folder 2)
      Includes carbon copies of correspondence between Moses and Guy Greer regarding post-war employment and public works.
    - N - General, 1935-1967; 216827 (Box 97, Folder 3)
      Includes a copy of a letter from HRL to Mohammed Naguib, and the speech "The Mission of the Liberal Arts" by Roy F. Nichols. Correspondents include Stephen C. Neill, Arthur C. Nielsen, Samuel I. Newhouse Jr., Harold Nicolson, and Isamu Noguchi.
    - Nast, Condé, 1933-1941; 216828 (Box 97, Folder 4)
      Includes the memorandum (possibly a retyped copy) "To the Vanity Fair Editors Concerning Their Suggestion to Turn Vanity Fair Into a Pictorial Weekly" which mentions Clare Brokaw (Clare Boothe Luce).
    - Needham, Maurice, 1956-1962; 216829 (Box 97, Folder 4)
    - Nehru, Madame Rajan K., 1963; 216830 (Box 97, Folder 4)
    - Niarchos, Stavros S., 1957-1963; 216831 (Box 97, Folder 4)
      Includes a "Summary of the Proceedings in the U.S.A. and England Between Sun Oil Company and World Tankers Corporation."
    - Nicolini, Franco, 1953; 216832 (Box 97, Folder 4)
      Includes HRL's interview with the Italian publication Valori titled "A Conversation With the Editor of FORTUNE on the Fortune of the Press."
    - Nimitz, Admiral Chester W., 1943-1963; 216833 (Box 97, Folder 4)
      Includes part of the script from the "March of Time" program with the statement made by Nimitz.
    - Norris, Charles G., 1938-1943; 216834 (Box 97, Folder 4)
    - Norton, Henry K., 1936; 216835 (Box 97, Folder 4)
    - O - General, 1933-1967; 216836 (Box 97, Folder 5)
      Correspondents include Lawrence F. O'Brien, Culbert L. Oslon, Sir David Ormsby Gore, and G. Bromley Oxnam.
    - O'Donnell, Emmet, 1951; 216837 (Box 97, Folder 6)
      Contains the foreword of an unidentified manuscript regarding the activities of the FEAF Bomber Command in the Korean War.
    - O'Hara, John, 1938-1949; 216843 (Box 97, Folder 6)
    - Olivetti, Roberto, 1953-1955; 216845 (Box 97, Folder 6)
    - On Kin, 1952; 216846 (Box 97, Folder 6)
      Includes a letter from Lyman Hoover of the Committee for a Free Asia, and correspondence and memoranda regarding the lunch in honor of the editor of The Burma Times.
    - Orton, William A., 1948; 216849 (Box 97, Folder 6)
      Includes the first draft of the article "Business and Ethics."
    - Oxnam, G. Bromley, 1947-1957; 216858 (Box 97, Folder 6)
    - P - General, 1933-1967; 216867 (Box 97, Folder 7)
      Correspondents include Shah Pahlavi (copy), Paul Theodore Prince Paleologue, Sandro Pallavicini, Arnold Palmer, Robert P. Patterson, and Linus Pauling.
    - Page, Arthur, 1933-1948; 216878 (Box 98, Folder 1)
    - Page, Ruth, 1950; 216879 (Box 98, Folder 1)
    - Palmer, Carleton H. and Winthrop B., 1936-1957; 216880 (Box 98, Folder 1)
      Includes a form letter to E.R. Squibb & Sons salesmen regarding advertising in early issues of LIFE, and an advertising brochure for the magazine Poetry London-New York.
    - Parker, G. B., 1935-1943; 216881 (Box 98, Folder 1)
    - Palmer, Paul, 1935-1937; 216882 (Box 98, Folder 1)
    - Paepke, Walter, 1936-1955; 216883 (Box 98, Folder 1)
      Includes a page proof of an advertisement for the Container Corporation of America drawn by Mei Mei Sze.
    - Parmentier, Douglas, 1938; 216884 (Box 98, Folder 1)
    - Parton, James, 1948; 216885 (Box 98, Folder 1)
      Includes an unsigned pre-incorporation subscription agreement for Independence, Inc. a Time Inc. venture into Los Angeles newspapers.
    - Patterson, Grove, 1940-1951; 216886 (Box 98, Folder 2)
      Includes the address delivered at the Convention of the Association of National Advertisers "The Shield of Democracy" in pamphlet form.
    - Patterson, Morehead, 1948-1962; 216887 (Box 98, Folder 2)
    - Patterson, Jr. Richard C., 1945-1959; 216888 (Box 98, Folder 2)
    - Paul VI (Pope), 1965-1966; 216889 (Box 98, Folder 2)
      Contains memoranda and correspondence dealing with publications resulting from the Pope's visit to the United States.
    - Pawley, William D., 1943-1952; 216890 (Box 98, Folder 2)
      Includes correspondence dealing with the political situation in Brazil and Latin America.
    - Pe-Ph - General, 1933-1967; 216892 (Box 98, Folder 3)
      Includes carbon copies of correspondence addressed to Westbrook Pegler. Correspondents include Gregory Peck, Ferdinand Pecora, J. C. Penney, Claude Pepper, Frances Perkins, Prince Peter of Greece, and Field Marshal A. Papagos.
    - Peden, Allen, 1933; 216893 (Box 98, Folder 4)
    - Pell, Claiborne, 1965; 216894 (Box 98, Folder 4)
    - Pella, Guiseppe (Premier), 1953-1955; 216895 (Box 98, Folder 4)
      Includes a letter from Pella to Giovanni Fummi.
    - Penton, Brian, 1944; 216896 (Box 98, Folder 4)
    - Percy, Charles H., 1959-1967; 216897 (Box 98, Folder 4)
    - Phelps, William Lyon, 1942-1943; 216898 (Box 98, Folder 4)
      Includes three photographs of barges and ships on the Mississippi River.
    - Pi-Py - General, 1933-1967; 216904 (Box 98, Folder 5)
      Correspondents include Mary Pickford, Charles Poletti, Lily Pons, Cole Porter, Charles E. Potter, Ralph F. Gates, and Pyo Wook Han.
    - Pike, James A., 1961-1964; 216916 (Box 98, Folder 6)
      Contains correspondence mostly regarding the Christian Anti-Communist Crusade.
    - Pitman, Paul, 1952-1963; 216917 (Box 98, Folder 6)
    - Pitzele, Merlyn S., 1948-1950; 216925 (Box 98, Folder 6)
      Includes typed notes of an interview with HRL for an article in Business Week.
    - Poling, Daniel, 1947-1964; 216939 (Box 98, Folder 6)
    - Pope, Arthur U., 1943-1949; 216945 (Box 98, Folder 6)
    - Porter, Charles O., 1959-1960; 216959 (Box 98, Folder 6)
    - Powel, Hartford, 1933-1948; 216970 (Box 98, Folder 7)
    - Price, Harry B. (Mr. and Mrs.), 1938-1955; 217008 (Box 98, Folder 7)
      Includes a page proof of the Gallup Poll article "Boycott of Japan and Embargo on War Materials Favored as U.S. Sympathy for China Rises," the paper "Pacific Strategy: A Key to American Defense," the booklet "Shall America Stop Arming Japan," and correspondence with memoranda from The American Committee for Non-Participation in Japanese Aggression.
    - Pulitzer, Jr. Joseph, 1938-1951; 217009 (Box 98, Folder 7)
    - Q - General, 1947-1967; 217010 (Box 99, Folder 1)
    - Quaroni (Ambassador), 1955; 217011 (Box 99, Folder 2)
      Includes a speech? in Italian titled "La Coesistenza" (coexistence) with a partial translation.
    - Quezon, Manuel, 1941-1943; 217012 (Box 99, Folder 2)
    - Ra-Re - General, 1933-1965; 217013 (Box 99, Folder 3)
      Correspondents include Ralph T. Reed, James B. Reston, and Paul Reynaud.
    - Radford, Admiral Arthur, 1953-1963; 217015 (Box 99, Folder 4)
    - Ramirez, Ramiro and William, 1967; 217016 (Box 99, Folder 4)
    - Ramsaye, Terry, 1933; 217017 (Box 99, Folder 4)
    - Read, David, 1954-1966; 217018 (Box 99, Folder 4)
    - Reed, Guy E., 1950; 217021 (Box 99, Folder 4)
      Includes the speech "Why Business Men Should Organize to Destroy Organized Crime" by Reed made before the Economic Club of Detroit.
    - Reeves, Harrison, 1932-1940; 217022 (Box 99, Folder 4)
    - Reid, Mrs. Ogden, 1939-1965; 217023 (Box 99, Folder 4)
    - Reiser, Oliver, 1964-1974; 217024 (Box 99, Folder 4)
    - Reston, James, 1953-1963; 217025 (Box 99, Folder 4)
    - Rh-Ry - General, 1933-1974; 217040 (Box 99, Folder 5)
      Includes a postcard with the image of the Eskimo in skin omiak hunting walrus in Alaska sent by Kermit Roosevelt. Correspondents include Admiral H. G. Rickover, Donald W. Riegle Jr., Reuben B. Robertson Jr., James S. Rockefeller, General K. E. Rockey, Ginger Rogers, George Romney, James Roosevelt, Quentin Roosevelt II, and Rosalind Russell.
    - Rhyne, Charles - Speeches and Writings, 1958-1959; 217081 (Box 99, Folder 6)
      Includes a copy of a note from President Eisenhower and the speeches "An Idea on the March," "World Law to Protect World Investment," "The Case of the Empty Courtroom: The Effect of the Connally Reservation on the International Court of Justice," "Building Beyond the Rule of Terror to a Law-ful World," "Statement Opening Boston Conference on World Peace Through Law," "A New Meaning and Mission for NATS Leadership in Creating a 'Law-ful' World," "A Program for Lawyers of the Americas: World Peace Through Law," and "Achieving World Peace Through Law."
    - Rhyne, Charles - Miscellaneous, 1958-1972; 217090 (Box 99, Folder 6)
    - Rickenbacker, Edward V., 1939-1963; 217091 (Box 99, Folder 6)
      Includes the speech made at the annual banquet of the Baseball Writers' Association, and a photograph of William Van Dusen.
    - Robbins, Richard, 1932-1937; 217099 (Box 99, Folder 7)
    - Roberts, Owen, 1948-1949; 217111 (Box 99, Folder 7)
      Includes the brochure "Blueprint for Freedom: The Federal Union Plan."
    - Robertson, Walter S., 1953-1955; 217119 (Box 99, Folder 7)
    - Robinson, H. C., 1933; 217131 (Box 99, Folder 7)
    - Rockefeller, David, 1958-1967; 217132 (Box 99, Folder 7)
      Includes a copy of a letter sent by Rockefeller to President Kennedy regarding the balance of payment problem.
    - Rockefeller, Jr. John D., 1933-1956; 217133 (Box 99, Folder 7)
    - Rockefeller, III John D., 1942-1963; 217148 (Box 99, Folder 7)
    - Rodman, Selden, 1942-1943; 217156 (Box 99, Folder 8)
    - Roosevelt, II Theodore, 1943; 217198 (Box 99, Folder 8)
    - Root, Wells, 1933-1943; 217215 (Box 99, Folder 8)
    - Roots, John McC., 1947-1966; 217237 (Box 100, Folder 1)
      Includes an outline titled "Ideological Preparedness for America," an issue of the magazine New World News, the article "Every Valley Shall be Exalted" by Jack Jones, an advertising leaflet for the play "Jotham Valley," and a photograph of Miami Mayor William M. Wolfarth with four pilots and copies of the publication An Idea Takes Wings.
    - Roots, Logan (Bishop of Hankow), 1935; 217238 (Box 100, Folder 1)
      Includes an issue of the newspaper Journal de Genève.
    - Roper, Elmo, 1942-1967; 217239 (Box 100, Folder 1)
      Includes a draft of the essay "Maybe the Republicans Really Won!"
    - Rosebery, Earl (Lord), 1942-1944; 217240 (Box 100, Folder 1)
    - Rosenberg, James N., 1958-1959; 217241 (Box 100, Folder 2)
    - Rosenberg, Louis, 1933; 217242 (Box 100, Folder 2)
      Includes the pamphlet "The Failure of Commercial Banking to Function and the Remedy" by R. G. Trippett.
    - Rosenblatt, Sol A., 1952; 217243 (Box 100, Folder 2)
      Includes a transcript of the Eleanor Morgan Satterlee Surrogate Court case and a statement made by Rosenblatt.
    - Ross, Emory, 1939-1943; 217244 (Box 100, Folder 2)
    - Rostow, Walt, 1954-1956; 217245 (Box 100, Folder 2)
    - Rothmore, Lord, 1939-1945; 217246 (Box 100, Folder 2)
    - Roxas, Manuel, 1946-1948; 217247 (Box 100, Folder 2)
    - Rubicam, Raymond, 1933-1966; 217248 (Box 100, Folder 2)
    - Ruppel, Louis, 1951-1952; 217249 (Box 100, Folder 2)
    - Rusconi, Edilio, 1955-1967; 217250 (Box 100, Folder 2)
    - Sa-Sf - General, 1933-1967; 217251 (Box 100, Folder 3)
      Correspondents include Antonio de Oliveira Salazar, Jonas Salk, Leverett Saltonstall, F. Bradford Morse, Leverett Saltonstall, Robert W. Sarnoff, Mario Scelba, William W. Scranton, and Count Carlo Sforza.
    - Sancton, Thomas, 1942-1943; 217252 (Box 100, Folder 4)
      Includes an outline for the story "Stamford Local."
    - Sarnoff, David, 1951-1971; 217253 (Box 100, Folder 4)
      Includes Sarnoff's speech "The Impact of Science Upon Society."
    - Sayre, Francis B., 1943-1948; 217254 (Box 100, Folder 4)
    - Scheftel, Stuart (folder 1 of 2), 1938-1949; 221357 (Box 100, Folder 4)
      Includes a letter to HRL dated 2 March 1938 regarding Scheftel's decision to halt publishing the magazine SPORTS ILLUSTRATED and a carbon copy of HRL's response.
    - Scheftel, Stuart (folder 2 of 2) - oversize, 1940; 221359 (Box OS-Small)
      Contains three issues of the magazine Young America.
    - Schuman, Frederick L., 1941; 217255 (Box 100, Folder 4)
      Includes a letter from Schuman to Clare Boothe Luce with the attached memorandum "India and the Present War."
    - Schuster, M. Lincoln, 1933-1962; 217256 (Box 100, Folder 4)
    - Sedgewick, Ellery, 1933; 217257 (Box 100, Folder 4)
      Includes a proposal for the magazine House Beautiful.
    - Selfridge, Jr. and Sr. Gordon, 1933-1938; 217258 (Box 100, Folder 4)
    - Seltzer, Louis, 1939-1964; 217259 (Box 100, Folder 4)
    - Selznick, David O. (folder 1 of 2), 1933-1945; 217261 (Box 100, Folder 5)
      Includes a telegram to HRL announcing the formation of Selznick International Pictures Incorporated, the proposed contract? for the distribution of "March of Time" in France, Belgium, Switzerland and Holland, and a memorandum describing a meeting with representatives of movie studios regarding the attitude of Hollywood toward LIFE. Correspondents include Reginald Ford and Russull Birdwell.
    - Selznick, David O. (folder 2 of 2), 1946-1961; 217262 (Box 101, Folder 1)
      Includes a memorandum regarding Time Inc.'s attitude toward the movies, and a 14 page telegram protesting an upcoming article with mentions of actresses, movies, and practices in Hollywood.
    - Servan-Schrieber, J. J. and J. C., 1954-1968; 217263 (Box 101, Folder 2)
    - Sevareid, Eric, 1946-1955; 217264 (Box 101, Folder 2)
    - Severinghaus, Leslie, 1933-1982; 217265 (Box 101, Folder 2)
    - Sewall, Sumner, 1943-1947; 217269 (Box 101, Folder 2)
      Includes Sewall's article under two different titles: "Post-War Peace" and "Dynamic Peace" with a critique by HRL.
    - Seymour, Charles, 1937-1947; 217270 (Box 101, Folder 2)
    - Sh-Sm - General (folder 1 of 2), 1933-1976; 217275 (Box 101, Folder 3)
      Includes a memorandum regarding a conversation between Italian President-elect Giovanni Gronchi and Dott Sillani. Correspondents include Sir Hartley Shawcross, Alan B. Shepard Jr., Igor I. Sikorsky, George J. Hecht, Osbert Sitwell, Alfred E. Smith, and Margaret Chase Smith.
    - Sm-Sz - General (folder 2 of 2), 1938-1967; 217276 (Box 101, Folder 4)
      Includes the statement titled "The Pacific Front" by Robert Aura Smith (dated 17 December 1941) and a memorandum titled "Culture Heroine" regarding Susan Sontag. Correspondents include Senator Willis Smith, Sam Snead, Brehon Somervell, Harrison E. Spangler, Francis Cardinal Spellman, and Ed Sullivan.
    - Sheed, Frank, 1955-1956; 217277 (Box 101, Folder 5)
    - Shelden, Alger, 1933-1965; 217278 (Box 101, Folder 5)
    - Sherwood, Robert, 1939-1945; 217279 (Box 101, Folder 5)
    - Simon, Richard L., 1939-1953; 217280 (Box 101, Folder 5)
    - Singh, J. J., 1948-1963; 217281 (Box 101, Folder 5)
      Includes the article "India's Publicity Abroad" by Singh.
    - Skouras, Spyros, 1944-1963; 217283 (Box 101, Folder 5)
      Includes a letter mentioning the movie "Cleopatra" and the election of John F. Kennedy.
    - Sloan, Jr. Alfred P., 1936-1963; 217285 (Box 101, Folder 5)
    - Smith, Charles D., 1935-1958; 217282 (Box 101, Folder 5)
    - Smith, Walter Bedell, 1954; 217286 (Box 101, Folder 6)
    - Smuts, Jan Christian, 1942; 217290 (Box 101, Folder 6)
      Includes correspondence from Thomas W. Lamont.
    - Snow, Edgar, 1941-1944; 217292 (Box 101, Folder 6)
    - Sokolasky, George E., 1933-1944; 217295 (Box 101, Folder 6)
    - Soong, T. V., 1942-1971; 217298 (Box 101, Folder 6)
    - Speare, Mrs. Dorothy, 1944-1947; 217301 (Box 101, Folder 6)
    - Spellman, Francis J., 1943-1966; 217305 (Box 101, Folder 6)
    - Spender, Sir Percy, 1953; 217306 (Box 101, Folder 6)
      Includes a memorandum regarding the business of Time-Life International in Australia.
    - St - General, 1933-1967; 217312 (Box 102, Folder 1)
      Includes the brochure "Is This Where You Stand?" from the Writers' War Board. Correspondents include Jules Stein, John C. Sterling, Robert T. Stevens, Edward Durell Stone, Beatrice Kaufman, Rex Stout, and Franz Josef Strauss.
    - Starr, Cornelius V., 1940-1962; 217313 (Box 102, Folder 2)
      Includes correspondence regarding the situation in Shanghai, China in 1940.
    - Stassen, Harold E., 1944-1966; 217314 (Box 102, Folder 2)
      Includes an original signed resolution conveying sincere appreciation to Stassen from the Bexar County Republican Executive Committee.
    - Steichen, Edward, 1935-1936, 1973; 217315 (Box 102, Folder 2)
    - Steinhardt, Laurence A., 1940-1949; 217316 (Box 102, Folder 2)
      Includes detailed letters regarding China, Japan, Soviet Union, and World War II.
    - Stern, J. David, 1935-1971; 217317 (Box 102, Folder 2)
    - Stewart, George, 1943-1950; 217318 (Box 102, Folder 2)
    - Stoves, Reverend A. P., 1937-1951; 217323 (Box 102, Folder 3)
      Includes a transcript of the lecture "An Historical Survey of American Church-State Relations."
    - Storey, Dean, 1952-1957; 217324 (Box 102, Folder 3)
    - Strauss, Lewis, 1953-1963; 217325 (Box 102, Folder 3)
    - Streit, Clarence K. (folder 1 of 2), 1939-1948; 217331 (Box 102, Folder 4)
      Includes a page proof of the advertisement "Defense Now News Union Now: A Proposal that the U.S. and the Six British Democracies form a Federal Union Before It Is Too Late," a draft of the article "The American Answer - Federal Union of the Free," a draft of a prospectus for an illustrated monthly magazine Headlight later changed to Freedom and Union, carbon copies of letters from Streit to Franklin and Eleanor Roosevelt, and other correspondence regarding the Federal Union movement.
    - Streit, Clarence K. (folder 2 of 2), 1948-1963; 217344 (Box 102, Folder 5)
      Includes galleys for the publication Union Now: A Proposal for An Atlantic Federal Union of the Free and of an advertisement for the book Freedom Against Itself, the pamphlet "Free Enterprise Makes for Peace," an issue of the magazine Freedom and Union, and a first draft of the "13-Year Report to Readers of 'Union Now.' "
    - Stuart, Leighton J., 1938-1966; 217350 (Box 102, Folder 6)
      Includes a carbon copy of a letter sent to Cordell Hull regarding Japanese aggression in China, and the prefatory note and foreword to the book Fifty Years in China: The Memoirs of John Leighton Stuart, Missionary in China.
    - Sudler, Carroll, 1942; 217354 (Box 102, Folder 6)
    - Su-Sw - General, 1932-1972; 217361 (Box 102, Folder 7)
      Includes a typescript copy of a form letter from the Communist Party, USA regarding Maurice Sugar.
    - Sulzberger, Arthur Hays, 1957-1963; 217365 (Box 102, Folder 8)
    - Swanberg, William A. - Quotes from HRL's Documents, circa 1970-1972; 217369 (Box 102, Folder 8)
      Contains lists of quotations from HRL's early letters, speeches, trip reports, memoranda to staff and other writings for possible use in the book Citizen Luce.
    - Swanberg, William A. - Miscellaneous, 1959-1976; 217381 (Box 102, Folder 8)
      Contains mostly correspondence, memoranda, and research materials regarding Swanberg's biography of Luce.
    - Swing, Raymond, 1942-1944; 217426 (Box 103, Folder 1)
    - Swope, Herbert B., 1936-1964; 217451 (Box 103, Folder 1)
      Includes Swope's radio remarks on the subject of public policy vs. public relations.
    - Symington, W. Stuart, 1943-1963; 217454 (Box 103, Folder 1)
    - T - General (folder 1 of 2), 1933-1967; 217467 (Box 103, Folder 2)
      Correspondents include Deems Taylor, Francis Henry Taylor, and Dan Thornton.
    - T - General (folder 2 of 2), 1938-1967; 217474 (Box 103, Folder 3)
      Includes a memorandum describing a meeting with Tiangfu F. Tsiang. Correspondents include Giuseppe Togni, Lynn A. Townsend, Gene Tunney, and Millard E. Tydings.
    - Taft, Charles P., 1937-1963; 217477 (Box 103, Folder 4)
    - Tasca, Henry J., 1954-1957; 217480 (Box 103, Folder 4)
    - Taubes, Frederic, 1959; 217485 (Box 103, Folder 4)
    - Taylor, Henry J., 1942-1958; 217496 (Box 103, Folder 4)
    - Taylor, Reese H., 1933-1960; 217504 (Box 103, Folder 4)
      Includes a page proof of an advertisement for the Union Oil Company of California, the essay "California - Terra Incognita" by Herman Phleger, and Taylor's commencement address at the Webb School of California "20 Minutes With My Sons."
    - Taylor, Vernon F., 1938-1949; 217508 (Box 103, Folder 4)
    - Teller, Dr. Edward, 1961-1964; 217509 (Box 103, Folder 4)
      Includes a transcript of a statement made by Dr. Teller to the New York State Defense Council.
    - Thacker, Earl, 1942-1946; 217510 (Box 103, Folder 5)
    - Thanat, Khoman, 1965-1966; 217511 (Box 103, Folder 5)
      Includes a letter from Governor Samuel P. Goddard.
    - Thomas, Lowell, 1934-1967; 217512 (Box 103, Folder 5)
    - Thornburg, Max W., 1941-1964; 217513 (Box 103, Folder 5)
      Includes a memorandum regarding World War II and Arabic countries, and a set of detailed memoranda dealing with oil policy and oil related issues in Mexico, Colombia, Peru, and Venezuela.
    - Thorne, Landon K. (Mr. and Mrs.), 1954-1961; 217514 (Box 103, Folder 6)
    - Thurston, Lorrin P., 1935-1960; 217520 (Box 103, Folder 6)
    - Tiarks, Henry F., 1950-1952; 217521 (Box 103, Folder 6)